Guide to the United Student Christian Council Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- USCC Committees and Commissions, Series III
  - Study Department
    - Pilot Study, 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 413)
    - Publicity Materials and Ideas (Box 36, Folder 414)
    - Questionnaire re. Member Movement Study and Program Materials, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 415)
    - Report, Christian Social Responsibility in the Field of Integration, n.d (Box 36, Folder 416)
    - Reports, Direction of the Study Department, 1949-1956 (Box 36, Folder 417)
    - Reports, re. Evangelism in the University, 1950-1953 (Box 36, Folder 418)
    - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 419)
    - Reports, Study Department Report to the Executive Committee, 1951-1956 (Box 36, Folder 420)
    - Study guides, Miscellaneous, circa 1950s (Box 161, Folder 1848)
    - Study guides, Miscellaneous, circa 1950s (Box 161, Folder 1849)
    - World Council of Churches Document Service: Christian Action in Society Series, n.d (Box 36, Folder 421)
    - WSCF Life and Mission of the Church Materials (Box 36, Folder 422)
  - World Student Christian Federation Committee
    - Committee Records
      - 3 Year Report of the USA sCms to the WSCF, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 423)
      - 3 Year Report: USCC Compiled Report, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 424)
      - 3 Year Report: YMCA, 1946-1949 (Box 36, Folder 425)
      - 6 Year Report: Research Material, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 426)
      - Administrative file of Charles Hein (Chairman of USCC), 1949-1950 (Box 37, Folder 427)
      - Advisory Committee for Life and Mission of the Church Program, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 428)
      - Circular Letters, 1949-1951 (Box 37, Folder 429)
      - Committee on Friendly Relations among Foreign Students: International Students and the Church, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 430)
      - Deschner's notes of WSCF Committee, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 431)
      - Directories, 1946-1947, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 432)
      - Finances, 1945, 1947, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 433)
      - Foreign Student Evangelism, 1950-1951 (Box 37, Folder 434)
      - Life and Mission of the Church Emphasis, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 435)
      - Meeting Agendas, 1945-1957 (Box 37, Folder 436)
      - Memos, 1945-1946, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 437)
      - Minutes, 1944-1957 (Box 38, Folder 438)
      - Minutes, American Friends of WSCF, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 439)
      - Minutes, American WSCF Officers, 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 440)
      - Minutes, WSCF USCC of Southern California, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 441)
      - Needs Projects, 1949-1950 (Box 38, Folder 442)
      - News Sheet, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 443)
      - Overseas Relief and Reconstruction, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 444)
      - Projects, 1950, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 445)
      - Play, Satan in the Federation, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 446)
      - Proposal for WSCF Conference in the United States of America, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 447)
      - Promotion Ideas and Materials, 1949-1950 (Box 38, Folder 448)
      - Proposed Budget and Projects, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 449)
      - Reports, Miscellaneous Reports from other organizations or individuals concerning WSCF, 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 450)
      - Reports, Miscellaneous USCC Reports Concerning WSCF, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 451)
      - Reports, WSCF Committee Reports to the USCC General Assembly, 1951, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 452)
      - Reports, The Whitby Documents including drafts, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 453)
      - Sub-Committee on Consultations, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 454)
      - Sub-Committee on Work and Study Projects, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 455)
      - Sub-Committee on WSCF Publication, 1945-1946 (Box 39, Folder 456)
      - Trustees of WSCF Operating Account, 1949-1950 (Box 39, Folder 457)
      - WSCF Filmstrip including script and correspondence re. production of filmstrip, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 458)
      - WSCF Record script, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 459)
    - Correspondence
      - WSCF Finance letter, 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 460)
      - Church World Service, 1944-1947 (Box 39, Folder 461)
      - WSCF Leadership Conference, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 462)
      - General, 1945-1947 (Box 39, Folder 463)
      - Approaches to foundations and individuals, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 464)
      - re. Financial matters, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 465)
      - Information about WSCF to student groups, 1946-1947 (Box 39, Folder 466)
      - Pledge letters, 1946-1947 (Box 39, Folder 467)
      - Finances, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 468)
      - Requests for The Task of the University by John Coleman, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 469)
      - Weller, Rena, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 470)
      - Church World Service, 1947-1948 (Box 40, Folder 471)
      - re. Exchange Students and Scholarships, 1947-1948 (Box 40, Folder 472)
      - Fund raising for WSCF projects such as the Belgium project, German sCm, Latin American Leaders Conference, Southeast Asian Training Conference, and WSCF-Bible Study program, 1947-1950 (Box 161, Folder 1854)
      - Contribution and Subscription (Kept as an example while the rest discarded), 1947-1951 (Box 40, Folder 473)
      - re. International Student Relief, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 474)
      - General, 1948-1949 (Box 40, Folder 475)
      - re. International Student Relief, 1948-1949 (Box 40, Folder 476)
      - re. Board Appropriations, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 477)
      - Church World Service, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 478)
      - Church World Service, 1949-1950 (Box 40, Folder 479)
      - General, 1949-1950 (Box 40, Folder 480)
      - Hein, Charles (Chairman of WSCF Committee), 1949-1950 (Box 40, Folder 481)
      - Hoh, David, 1950-1951 (Box 41, Folder 482)
      - Rhinesmith, Eleanor, 1950-1951 (Box 41, Folder 483)
      - re. Contribution and Subscription with the WSCF Geneva office, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 484)
      - re. Foreign Student Evangelization, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 485)
      - General, 1951-1952 (Box 41, Folder 486)
      - re. WSCF Committee meetings, 1951-1952 (Box 41, Folder 487)
      - re. Church World Service, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 488)
      - re. Representatives to WSCF Committee, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 489)
      - re. WSCF leaflets, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 489a)
      - General, 1954-1956 (Box 41, Folder 490)
      - re. Financial support for various international sCm projects, 1955-1956 (Box 41, Folder 491)
      - General, 1956-1957 (Box 41, Folder 492)
      - re. Finances, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 493)
      - re. WSCF Committee meeting in St. Louis, MO, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 494)
    - Programs and Projects
      - WSCF Day of Prayer
        - Correspondence and printed Day of Prayer program, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 495)
        - Program and galley proofs, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 496)
        - Reports on World Day of Prayer, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 497)
        - Requests for Day of Prayer programs, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 498)
        - Correspondence and program, 1948 (Box 42, Folder 499)
        - Correspondence and program, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 500)
        - Correspondence, galley proof of program, and program, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 501)
        - Circular letters, correspondence, poster, and program packet, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 502)
        - Circular letters, correspondence, and program packet, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 503)
        - Day of Prayer evaluations, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 504)
        - Committee assignments and flyer, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 505)
        - Day of Prayer printing, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 506)
        - Promotional materials, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 507)
      - WSCF Federation Fellowship--New York City
        - WSCF Weekend, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 508)
        - WSCF Federation Fellowship, 1949-1951 (Box 42, Folder 509)
        - Correspondence, re. program coordinating, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 510)
      - WSCF Speakers and Visitors
        - Aye, Ma, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 511)
        - Birch, Charles, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 512)
        - Bridston, Keith, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 513)
        - Elliot, Roland, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 514)
        - Giles, Leila, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 515)
        - de Haller, Marie-Jeanne, 1948-1950 (Box 43, Folder 516)
        - de Haller, Marie-Jeanne, 1950-1951 (Box 43, Folder 517)
        - Hoffman, Bengt, 1947, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 518)
        - Koo, T.Z.: Biographical info and photographs, 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 519)
        - Koo, T.Z.: Requests for speaker and travel arrangements, 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 520)
        - Koo, T.Z.: Itineraries, 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 521)
        - Koo, T.Z.: Correspondence with USCC, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 522)
        - Koo, T.Z.: Federation Speaker's Account and itineraries, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 523)
        - Koo, T.Z.: Summer schedule, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 524)
        - Koo, T.Z.: Travel arrangements, September 1946-January 1947 (Box 44, Folder 525)
        - Koo, T.Z.: Travel arrangements, February-March 1947 (Box 44, Folder 526)
        - Koo, T.Z.: Travel arrangements, March-May 1947 (Box 44, Folder 527)
        - Maury, Philippe, 1946-1947 (Box 44, Folder 528)
        - Maury, Philippe, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 529)
        - Maury, Philippe, 1954-1956 (Box 45, Folder 530)
        - Miscellaneous speakers and visitors, 1946-1947 (Box 45, Folder 531)
        - Miscellaneous speakers and visitors, 1948-1950 (Box 45, Folder 532)
        - Rodhe, Birgit, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 533)
        - Schanke, Andreas, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 534)
        - Speakers Account, 1948-1949 (Box 45, Folder 535)
        - Speakers in USA for WSCF, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 536)
        - Ting, K.H., 1949-1950 (Box 45, Folder 537)
        - t'Hooft, Visser, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 538)
        - WSCF Staff in USA, 1947-1948 (Box 45, Folder 539)
      - WSCF Summer Projects
        - Program planning for ecumenical international work and study camp, Bievres, France, April-July 1947 (Box 45, Folder 540)
        - Correspondence, re. Delegates to work and study camp, Bievres, France, July-August 1947 (Box 46, Folder 541)
        - Correspondence with delegates and evaluations re. work and study camp at Bievres, France, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 542)
        - Student in Industry Work Camp program planning, Brantford, Ontario, June-September 1947 (Box 46, Folder 543)
        - Summer projects, 1946-1947 (Box 160, Folder 1841)
        - Reports, Work camps in Bievres, France and Brantford, Ontario, 1947-1948 (Box 46, Folder 544)
        - Agency correspondence re. conferences and projects, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 1841)
        - Correspondence, re. Money owed from previous year's travel, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 1842)
        - Correspondence, re. Overseas travel, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 1843)
        - Correspondence, re. Overseas travel, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 1844)
        - Dutch project, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 1845)
        - Possible summer projects, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 545)
        - Inquiries about summer projects, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 546)
        - Inquires about summer projects, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 547)
        - Correspondence, re. International Work-Study Project, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 548)
        - Reconstruction work camp in Mainz, Germany: Program planning, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 549)
        - Reconstruction project in Mainz, Germany: Program planning and evaluations, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 550)
        - Student in Industry Project, Brantford, Ontario, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 551)
        - World Council of Churches sponsored work camps, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 552)
        - Correspondence, re. Overseas travel, 1949 (Box 160, Folder 1846)
        - Correspondence, re. Summer projects, 1949 (Box 160, Folder 1847)
        - Summer projects includes promotional material, 1949-1950 (Box 47, Folder 553)
        - Inquiries about summer projects, 1950, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 554)
        - Africa Student Seminar, Delegate list, 1958 (Box 160, Folder 1848)
  - Other Committees
    - By Laws Committee
      - Correspondence and recommendations from the National Assembly of the Student Christian Association Movement, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 554a)
    - Ecumenical Advisory Committee
      - Circulars, 1956-1958 (Box 47, Folder 555)
      - Clusters: Names of schools, locations, and classifications, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 556)
      - Consultation on Meaning of Unity, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 557)
      - Correspondence, re. State ecumenical activities, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 558)
      - Correspondence, re. meetings and nominations to committee, 1956-1957 (Box 47, Folder 559)
      - Correspondence, General, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 560)
      - Correspondence, re. State ecumenical activities, 1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 561)
      - Correspondence, Local ecumenical councils, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 562)
      - Memos, 1956-1957 (Box 47, Folder 563)
      - Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 47, Folder 564)
      - Questions on the organization of student groups, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 565)
      - Regional sCm conferences, 1955-1958 (Box 48, Folder 566)
      - Reports: re. Cooperative work on campuses, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 567)
      - Survey re. State ecumenical councils, 1958 (Box 48, Folder 568)
    - Committee on Evangelism
      - Reports and correspondence re. evangelism, 1950, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 569)
    - Committee for Work Among Graduate Students
      - Book: The Presence of the Kingdom by Jacques Ellul, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 570)
      - Circular letters, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 571)
      - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 48, Folder 572)
      - Graduate Study Group on "Christian Liberty and Academic Freedom", 1954 (Box 48, Folder 573)
      - Information from other organizations, 1953-1956 (Box 48, Folder 574)
      - Law conference proposals, 1955-1958 (Box 48, Folder 575)
      - Minutes, 1953-1956 (Box 48, Folder 576)
      - Questionnaire for medical students, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 577)
      - Report, "Evangelism Among Graduate Students" includes draft, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 578)
      - Reports, Reports from Committee for Work Among Graduate Students, 1953-1954 (Box 49, Folder 579)
      - Reports, Two Law School Consultations, 1954-1955 (Box 49, Folder 580)
      - Report, "USCC Survey on Christian Work in Medical Schools in the U.S.A. and Canada", 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 581)
      - Study Guides, "Study Outline for Medical Students" and "Euthanasia: a Study Guide" by Wouter Bosch, Delbert Hlavinka, and Kenneth Spilman, 1945, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 582)
      - Survey, Graduate work within sCm groups, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 583)
      - Survey, Graduate work on campuses includes notes by Bryant Drake, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 584)
    - Looking Ahead Committee
      - Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 585)
      - Memos, 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 586)
      - Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 587)
      - Notes of John Deschner, circa 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 588)
      - Papers I, III-IX from the committee, 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 589)
      - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 590)
      - Reports, "The Organization of Student Christians Work in the U.S.A.," "Digest of Responses to the Preliminary Report of the Commission on the Message and Mission of the Student YMCA," "A Statement about the National Student YWCA and Some of the Questions It Faces Today, and "The Commission on Message and Mission of the Student YWCA", 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 591)
      - Working papers, 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 592)
    - Organization Committee
      - Correspondence, General, 1944-1949 (Box 49, Folder 593)
      - Correspondence, re. Proposed professional workers association, 1946-1948 (Box 50, Folder 594)
      - Correspondence, re. Attendance to the Organization Committee March 14-16 consultation, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 595)
      - Correspondence, re. Professional training study, 1947-1948 (Box 50, Folder 596)
      - Correspondence, re. Attendance to the April 7-11 meeting, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 597)
      - Correspondence, re. Professional workers study, 1949-1950 (Box 50, Folder 598)
      - Churchmanship statements, 1947-1949 (Box 50, Folder 599)
      - Consultation on Churchmanship and Professional Training, Yonkers, New York, March 14-16, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 600)
      - Consultation on Patterns of Local Cooperative Work, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 601)
      - Enlarged Meeting of the USCC Organization Committee, Bernardsville, New Jersey, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 602)
      - Memos, 1945-1949 (Box 50, Folder 603)
      - Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 51, Folder 604)
      - Minutes, 1946-1949 (Box 51, Folder 605)
      - Papers, re. Ecumenical Cooperation on College Campuses, 1945-1947 (Box 51, Folder 606)
      - Professional Workers' Association Research: Triennial Church Workers Conference, 1932-1936 (Box 51, Folder 607)
      - Professional Workers' Association Research: Triennial Church Workers Conference, 1936-1937 (Box 51, Folder 608)
      - Professional Workers' Association Research: Triennial Church Workers Conference, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 609)
      - Professional Workers' Study includes correspondence and final report A Study of the Need for and Possible Functions of a National Professional Student Religious Workers' Association by Walter Kuyaski, 1949-1951 (Box 51, Folder 609)
      - Projected Plans, 1947-1948 (Box 51, Folder 610)
      - Questionnaire re. Cooperative Work on Campuses, 1946-1946 (Box 51, Folder 611)
      - Report, Report of the Organization Committee to the United Student Christian Council, 1944-1947 (Box 52, Folder 612)
      - Research materials, Practical Steps in Vitalizing the Campus Religious Program by Charles Ketcham and Religion in the State University by Clarence Prouty Shedd, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 613)
      - Survey, Campus Workers Survey, circa 1950 (Box 52, Folder 614)
    - Personnel Committee
      - Correspondence, Search for an Executive Secretary, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 615)
      - Correspondence, General, 1946-1948, 1951-1952 (Box 52, Folder 616)
      - Correspondence, Search for an Executive Secretary and a Study Secretary, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 617)
      - Correspondence, General, 1954-1957 (Box 52, Folder 618)
      - Memos, Minutes, and Reports, 1945-1952 (Box 52, Folder 619)
    - Political Commission
      - Circular Letters, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 620)
      - Correspondence, Formation of the Commission, 1948-1949 (Box 52, Folder 621)
      - Correspondence, Ellis, Bill, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 622)
      - Correspondence, General, 1950-1951 (Box 52, Folder 623)
      - Correspondence, Stringfellow, William, 1950-1951 (Box 52, Folder 624)
      - Correspondence, Literature Requests, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 625)
      - Correspondence, Nominations to the Commission, 1951-54 (Box 53, Folder 626)
      - Correspondence, General, 1954-1955 (Box 53, Folder 627)
      - Correspondence, re. Coordinating Study on Theological Bases, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 628)
      - Correspondence, re. Freedom and Responsibility study group, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 629)
      - Correspondence, re. Social Issues and Direction of the Commission, 1955-1958 (Box 53, Folder 630)
      - Dialogue between French sCm and USCC, 1952-1953 (Box 53, Folder 631)
      - Directories and Reports of the Commission, 1950-1957 (Box 53, Folder 632)
      - Institute of Ethics and Politics: Articles of Operation, Proposals, and Reports, 1953-1957 (Box 53, Folder 633)
      - Institute of Ethics and Politics: Correspondence, 1953-1957 (Box 53, Folder 634)
      - Memos, 1948-1958 (Box 53, Folder 635)
      - Minutes, 1950-1958 (Box 53, Folder 636)
      - Papers, A Theologically Based Interpretation of Politics by Bill Miller, The Theological Basis for Christian Political Concern by Prentis Pemberton, and Some Thoughts on the American sCm in Politics by William Stringfellow, 1950-1951 (Box 53, Folder 637)
      - Possible Creation of a Summer Institute of Theology and Politics, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 638)
      - Publications from Other Organizations including Memos from WSCF Political Commission, 1951-1956 (Box 54, Folder 639)
      - Report, Law Conference sponsored by the World Council of Churches and the Ecumenical Institute, 1950-1952 (Box 54, Folder 640)
      - Reports, Reports to the USCC General Assembly, 1957-1958 (Box 54, Folder 641)
      - Topical, Correspondence, news clippings, and Paul Schrading's statement to the Senate on the Judiciary Subcommittee on Immigration and Naturalization, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 642)
      - Topical, Intellectual Freedom, 1957 (Box 54, Folder 643)
      - Topical, International Affairs, 1954-1958 (Box 54, Folder 644)
      - Topical, Nuclear Disarmament, 1957-1958 (Box 54, Folder 645)
      - Topical, Workers' Rights, circa 1957 (Box 54, Folder 646)
      - Transcripts of Radio Program Religion at the News Desk, 1951-1952 (Box 54, Folder 647)
      - Willmott Case, 1952 (Box 54, Folder 648)
    - Program and Project Committee
      - Correspondence, 1945-1950 (Box 54, Folder 649)
      - Memos and Minutes, 1945, 1948-1950 (Box 54, Folder 650)
      - Reports, re. Evangelism in the University, 1949-1951 (Box 54, Folder 651)
    - Publications Committee
      - Agenda Pending for October 28, 1947 meeting (Box 55, Folder 652)
      - Correspondence, General, 1945-1948 (Box 55, Folder 653)
      - Correspondence, re. Ecumenical Directory, 1947 (Box 55, Folder 654)
      - Correspondence, re. Acquiring Foreign Publications, 1948 (Box 55, Folder 655)
      - Correspondence, re. Creation of a sCm Press, 1947-1948 (Box 55, Folder 656)
      - Correspondence, Reprint of World Student Christian Federation: the First Thirty-Five Years by Ruth Rouse, 1948 (Box 55, Folder 657)
      - Correspondence, WSCF Publications, 1948 (Box 55, Folder 658)
      - Correspondence, Religious Book Club, 1950-1952 (Box 55, Folder 659)
      - Clip Art, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 660)
      - Communique, Art and Ideas, 1947 (Box 55, Folder 661)
      - Communique,, Mailing List, 1952, 1955-1956 (Box 55, Folder 662)
      - Communique, Pending Material, 1946-1947 (Box 55, Folder 663)
      - Communique, Pending Material, 1947-1949 (Box 55, Folder 664)
      - Communique, Pending Material, 1949-1952 (Box 55, Folder 665)
      - Communique, Pending Material, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 666)
      - Communique, Pending Material, 1955-1956 (Box 56, Folder 667)
      - Ecumenical Student Workbook, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 668)
      - Ecumenical Student Workbook Reviews, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 669)
      - Draft, Handbook for Religious Workers, 1948 (Box 56, Folder 670)
      - Literature Associates Plan, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 671)
      - Newspaper clippings re. USCC Creation, 1945 (Box 56, Folder 672)
      - News Releases, 1946-1947, 1949-1952 (Box 56, Folder 673)
      - News Service, 194-1950 (Box 56, Folder 674)
      - Memos and Minutes, 1945-1949 (Box 56, Folder 675)
      - Reports, Reports of the Publication Committee and "Cooperation of Protestant Campus Religious Organizations" by Robert R. Sanks, 1946-1950 (Box 56, Folder 676)
    - Religion in Higher Education Committee
      - Correspondence, General, 1945-1947 (Box 56, Folder 677)
      - Correspondence, re. John Coleman's (WSCF secretary) Visit to U.S.A., 1947-1948 (Box 56, Folder 678)
      - Correspondence, re. John Coleman's Visit includes Speaking Requests, 1947-1948 (Box 56, Folder 679)
      - Correspondence, re. John Coleman's Visit includes Itineraries, 1948 (Box 57, Folder 680)
      - Correspondence, General, 1948-1950 (Box 57, Folder 681)
      - Mailing List, 1948-1949 (Box 57, Folder 682)
      - Memos and Minutes include NICC Consultation, 1945-1948 (Box 57, Folder 683)
      - Newsletter, College and Church: Educational News Bulletin For Those Interested in Christian Higher Education issued by National Commission on Christian Higher Education, 1946-1947 (Box 57, Folder 684)
      - Reports, Reports of the Research in Higher Education Committee, The Christian Task of an American Student Christian Group in 1948-49, 1948-1949 (Box 57, Folder 685)
      - Research Material re. Christianity in Higher Education, 1946-1952 (Box 57, Folder 686)